Examining each blank issue:

[Problem #2] 諛묒쨪 移??⑥뼱? 愿꾪샇 ?덉뿉 二쇱뼱吏??⑥뼱???섎?媛 ?쒕줈 ?ㅻⅨ 寃껋??
Desc: 
Choices: ['Her mother was a <u>celebrated</u> actress. (famous)', 'Paul Scofield gave an <u>exquisite</u> performance. (excellent)', 'Wash the fish and take off the <u>scales</u> with a knife. (measures)', "She's on study <u>leave</u> until the end of September. (vacation)"]

[Problem #25] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 怨듯넻?쇰줈 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: You should have brought to children how to use their allowance. A rise in pay was nothing to write about.
Choices: ['attic', 'base', 'ground', 'home']

[Problem #33] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 怨듯넻?쇰줈 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Perceptions are . A single oak tree may seem large compared to a person, though it is small compared to the average redwood tree. In other words, things in nature are large or small, and new or old, according to the measure and the comparison involved. In view of this, it is easy to understand why time is . A minute seems like a long time to a person sitting on a hot stove, though it is nothing in terms of the average human life. Similarly, this life time is a passing moment in the history of the universe.
Choices: ['absolute', 'limited', 'relative', 'measurable']

[Problem #34] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: As early as the stage when human groups subsisted wholly by gathering and hunting, they were already making a strong imprint on the landscape. Their chief agent in doing so was fire. Fire is self-generating: its heat causes further material to ignite. As long as fuel and air are present, the fire will continue to burn and spread. Once human groups came to possess fire, therefore, they were in a position not only to prolong the burning of a single fire but also to reproduce it, to use it for making other fires. In a way, the very word fire is ambiguous and somewhat misleading, since it may refer both to a fire ??a singular, isolated event ??and to fire in general ??a process that occurs over and over again. The point is that with a fire people could continually make more fires. Their control of fire enabled them . And this is what they did. Going from place to place, they would light a campfire wherever they decided to stay.
Choices: ['to proliferate fire', 'to keep a single fire', 'to improve their mobility', 'to develop entertainment']

[Problem #49] ?ㅼ쓬 以?諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅???⑥뼱??
Desc: Emily is a writer and is always writing things down. Even when she can't find paper, she scrambles to find envelopes, napkins, anything she can use to write down her thoughts. She does this because she is both realistic and disciplined enough to know humans run across too many ideas to remember all of them or even most of them. Good ideas come floating into our heads and will easily float out. Writers acknowledge they carry around a notebook so that the best of those ideas can make it to paper. You don't have to be a writer, however, to have good ideas floating through you. Keep a notebook and pen and you will be able to hold onto those floating thoughts.
Choices: ['neat', 'handy', 'fancy', 'remote']

[Problem #74] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: It is now clear, from the results of the first research studies of this subject, dating from the 1960s, that all of these opinions are wrong. <u>( A )</u> The first step in considering the nature of sign language is to eradicate traditional misconceptions about its structure and function. <u>( B )</u> Popular opinions about the matter are quite plain: sign language is not a real language but little more than a system of sophisticated gesturing; signs are simply pictorial representations of external reality; and because of this, there is just one sign language, which can be understood all over the world. <u>( C )</u> A clear distinction must be drawn, first of all, between sign language and gesture. To sign is to use the hands in a conscious, ?쐖erbal??manner to express the same range of meaning as would be achieved by speech. <u>( D )</u>
Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D']

[Problem #110] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: The above passage suggests that the conversion to the metric system should be .
Choices: ['drastic', 'exigent', 'gradual', 'essential']

[Problem #111] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: ?ㅼ쓬 湲???쎄퀬 吏덈Ц???듯븯?쒖삤. The United States and Canada will someday join the 95 percent of the world that uses the metric rather than the English system of measurement. Inches will become centimeters, pounds will become kilograms, quarts will become liters, and degrees Fahrenheit will become degrees centigrade (also called Celsius). The conversion to the metric system will not be easy, however, and will require enormous amounts of money and time. For example, every piece of machinery in every factory and every office will have to be replaced. Furthermore, every machine and tool that makes, repairs, or supplies another piece of equipment will have to be changed. Therefore, although the United States and Canada are committed to ?쐅oing metric,??it will not happen next week or even next year. 臾?0. The above passage suggests that the conversion to the metric system should be .
Choices: ['Are you following me?', 'Are you rooting for me?', 'Can you just pick one now?', 'Are you up and about sooner or later?']

[Problem #112] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: ?ㅼ쓬 湲???쎄퀬 吏덈Ц???듯븯?쒖삤. The United States and Canada will someday join the 95 percent of the world that uses the metric rather than the English system of measurement. Inches will become centimeters, pounds will become kilograms, quarts will become liters, and degrees Fahrenheit will become degrees centigrade (also called Celsius). The conversion to the metric system will not be easy, however, and will require enormous amounts of money and time. For example, every piece of machinery in every factory and every office will have to be replaced. Furthermore, every machine and tool that makes, repairs, or supplies another piece of equipment will have to be changed. Therefore, although the United States and Canada are committed to ?쐅oing metric,??it will not happen next week or even next year. 臾?0. The above passage suggests that the conversion to the metric system should be .
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #116] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: As soon as we are born, the world gets to work on us and transforms us from merely biological into social units. Every human being at every stage of history or pre-history is born into a society and from his earliest years is moulded by that society. The language which he speaks is not an individual inheritance, but a social acquisition from the group in which he grows up. In a word, the individual apart from society would be both speechless and mindless. The lasting fascination of the Robinson Crusoe myth is due to its attempt to imagine an individual independent of society. The attempt . Robinson is not an abstract individual, but an Englishman from York; he carries his Bible with him and prays to his tribal God. The myth quickly bestows on him his Man Friday; and the building of a new society begins.
Choices: ['fails', 'repeats', 'succeeds', 'helps']

[Problem #120] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 怨듯넻?쇰줈 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: In the past few decades, governments have undertaken to control both prices and output in the agricultural sector, largely in response to the pressures of the farmers themselves. In the absence of such control, farm prices tend to more than do most other prices, and the incomes of farmers to an even greater degree. Not only are incomes in agriculture unstable, but they also tend to be lower than incomes in other economic sectors.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #175] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: In other words, our behavior is neither wholly determined by our genes nor wholly free from them. Grub's birth rekindled my interest in the nature vs. nurture debate, which was at that time producing bitter arguments in scientific circles. ( A ) Were we humans mainly the product of our genetic makeup or the product of our environment? ( B ) In recent years, these flames of controversy have died down, and it is now accepted that in all animals with reasonably complex brains, adult behavior is acquired through a mix of inherited traits and experience gained as the individual goes through life. ( C ) The more sophisticated an animal's brain, the greater the role that learning is likely to play in shaping its behavior, and the more variation we shall find between one individual and another. ( D ) And the information acquired and lessons learned during infancy and childhood, when behavior is at its most flexible, are likely to have particular significance.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #193] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: The digital world offers us many advantages, but if we yield to that world too completely we may lose the privacy we need to develop a self. Activities that require time and careful attention, like serious reading, are at risk; we read less and skim more as the Internet occupies more of our lives. And there?셲 a link between self-hood and reading slowly, rather than scanning for quick information, as the Web encourages us to do. Recent work in sociology and psychology suggests that reading books, a private experience, is an important aspect of coming to know who we are.
Choices: ['In Praise of Slow Reading', 'In Praise of Artificial Memory', 'In Praise of Digital World', 'In Praise of Private Life']

[Problem #195] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋?? Such large numbers are necessary since blood reserves are perishable and constantly need to be replenished. New York City Blood Center has experienced a constant shortage in blood donation. ( A ) To meet the needs, approximately 2,000 people need to donate blood every day to maintain its supplies. ( B ) One pint of donated blood can save up to three lives. ( C ) And one out of every three people will need a life-saving transfusion at some point in their lifetimes. ( D ) Donate blood through the New York City Blood Center.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #239] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Picture books are often considered to be only for the very young. Picture books are defined by their format rather than their content. Picture books may be of any genre, including poetry. They are unique because illustrations and text share the job of telling the story or teaching content. ( A ) No other type of literature works in the same manner. ( B ) Yet, picture books?뷹rom rugged board books for babies to the mysterious tales of Chris Van Allsburg, which adults appreciate wholeheartedly?뷷xist for a wide range of readers. ( C ) In today's publishing world, they have ascended to a true art form. ( D ) As full-color printing processes have improved and the demand for quality picture books has increased, some of our best artists and authors spend at least part of their creative lives expressing themselves in the picture book form.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #285] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: That plunge in poverty levels is truly one of the greatest achievements in human history. Welfare helps alleviate poverty. But growth can end it. Asia's example over the past half-century teaches that there are two critical ways to raise incomes: create jobs ??and create more jobs. And the way to do that is to boost economic growth. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #297] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: Teaching is also one of the few jobs where you can say you are making a significant and positive impact on the world around you. The rewards that come from teaching are numerous. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #318] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: But the truth is, after you successfully make it through this problem, there will be another problem to face. Some people are convinced that life is simply a series of problems to be solved. The sooner they get through with the problem they are facing, the sooner they will be happy. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #331] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Fortunately, however, the heavy supper she had eaten caused her to become tired and ready to fall asleep. Various duties awaited me on my arrival. I had to sit with the girls during their hour of study. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #355] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: However, should understanding not occur, you will find yourself soon becoming drowsy. Dictionaries are your most reliable resources for the study of words. Yet the habit of using them needs to be cultivated. Of course, it can feel like an annoying interruption to stop your reading and look up a word. You might tell yourself that if you keep going, you would eventually understand it from the context. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #379] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: If neither surrendered, the two exchanged blows until one was knocked out. The ancient Olympics provided athletes an opportunity to prove their fitness and superiority, just like our modern games. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #395] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: The same thinking can be applied to any number of goals, like improving performance at work. The happy brain tends to focus on the short term. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #419] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: But there is also clear evidence that millennials, born between 1981 and 1996, are saving more aggressively for retirement than Generation X did at the same ages, 22 節?7. Millennials are often labeled the poorest, most financially burdened generation in modern times. Many of them graduated from college into one of the worst labor markets the United States has ever seen, with a staggering load of student debt to boot.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #440] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: And working offers more than financial security. Why do workaholics enjoy their jobs so much? Mostly because working offers some important advantages. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #452] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: The comparison of the heart to a pump, however, is a genuine analogy. An analogy is a figure of speech in which two things are asserted to be alike in many respects that are quite fundamental. Their structure, the relationships of their parts, or the essential purposes they serve are similar, although the two things are also greatly dissimilar. Roses and carnations are not analogous. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #461] ?ㅼ쓬 ??붿쓽 ?먮쫫?쇰줈 蹂댁븘 諛묒쨪 移?怨녹뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : Did we finish packing all the orders?
B : No, we still have to do about ten more.

A : I'm tired of packing this stuff.
B : Maybe we could finish it later.

A : Sure, we could do it tomorrow morning.
B : O.K.
Choices: ['Those were the days.', "Let's call it a day.", "Why don't we call it off now?", "You know we don't have all day."]

[Problem #466] ?ㅼ쓬 諛묒쨪 移?怨녹뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: All is a continuous supply of food and water.
Choices: ['what is needed', 'which is needed', 'the things needed', 'that is needed']

[Problem #467] ?ㅼ쓬 諛묒쨪 移?怨녹뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: Reviews on caffeine and conception . One study of 2,817 women found no effect of caffeine on their chances of conceiving, while another of 1,909 women linked more than 300 milligrams of caffeine daily to a delay in conception.
Choices: ['conflict', 'coincide', 'make sense', 'manifest themselves']

[Problem #486] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: There are two excellent television programs scheduled tonight, but I can see only one of them because they are .
Choices: ['indisputable', 'concurrent', 'matchless', 'indispensable']

[Problem #501] 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: One bacterium that survives keeps replicating because it is not to the drug treatment.
Choices: ['curable', 'susceptible', 'prosperous', 'reproductive']

[Problem #508] ??붿쓽 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : Would you like to get some coffee?
B : That's a good idea.

A : Should we buy Americano or Cafe-Latte?
B : It doesn't matter to me.

A : I think I'll get Americano.
B : Sounds great to me.
Choices: ['Not really.', 'Suit yourself.', 'Come see for yourself.', 'Maybe just a handful or so.']

[Problem #509] ??붿쓽 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : 
B : Today is Monday, so you can have it until next Monday.

A : Can I have the book for a few more days?
B : No. Books borrowed should be returned within one week.

A : Is there any way to keep this book for around 10 days?
B : Well, I'm afraid there isn't. You'll just have to renew the book for another week.
Choices: ['What date is it?', 'When is this book due?', "I'd like to return this book.", 'This book can be checked out in due form, right?']

[Problem #510] ??붿쓽 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : Are you ready to go to the party, Amy?
B : I don't know whether I can go. I'm feeling a little sick, and my dress is really not that nice. Maybe you should just go without me.

A : Come on, Amy. Stop . I know you too well. You're not sick. What is the real root of the problem?
Choices: ['shaking a leg', 'hitting the ceiling', 'holding your horses', 'beating around the bush']

[Problem #529] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: The executives should estimate their debt-to-income ratios to see whether they run the risk of becoming .
Choices: ['insolvent', 'inverted', 'distracted', 'decoded']

[Problem #533] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: One custom that is common at weddings in the United States is throwing rice at the bride and groom as they leave the place where the wedding ceremony has just been held. No one knows exactly why people throw rice. One explanation is that the rice assures that the couple will have many children. If this is true, then the custom is not always a good one now because .
Choices: ['a lot of couples do not want many children', 'many people are pleased about it', 'many couples go on honeymoon the next day', 'it is unreasonable to clear away rice after the ceremony']

[Problem #535] ?ㅼ쓬 ??붿쓽 ?먮쫫?쇰줈 蹂댁븘 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : You know, I'm getting transferred to Seoul.
B : Seoul? Is that good or bad?

A : Oh, I was hoping for it.
B : .
Choices: ['I really wanted to go to Seoul', "Oh, it's not easy for me", "In that case, I'm happy for you", 'I appreciate your patience']

[Problem #536] ?ㅼ쓬 ??붿쓽 ?먮쫫?쇰줈 蹂댁븘 鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A : It doesn't make sense. Why should the power go off all of a sudden and the phone line?
B : Maybe some kind of an electrical storm or something.

A : Sky's just as blue as anything. Not a cloud. No lightening. No thunder. Nothing. How could it be a storm?
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #540] ?ㅼ쓬 湲???쎄퀬 ?꾨옒 臾몄옣??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Euthanasia generally refers to mercy killing, the voluntary ending of the life of someone who is terminally or hopelessly ill. Euthanasia has become a legal, medical and ethical issue over which opinion is divided. Euthanasia can be either active or passive. Active euthanasia means that a physician or other medical personnel takes a deliberate action that will induce death. Passive euthanasia means letting a patient die for lack of treatment or suspending treatment that has begun. A good deal of the controversy about mercy killing stems from the decision- making process. Who decides if a patient is to die? This issue had not been established legally in the United States. The matter is left to state law, which usually allows the physician in charge to suggest the option of death to a patient's relatives, especially if the patient is brain-dead. The article suggests that euthanasia should be .
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #542] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: To avoid death duty, the man the greater part of his property to his only son as soon as he retired.
Choices: ['made up', 'made over', 'made out', 'made up for']

[Problem #543] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: The viability of reclaimed water for indirect potable reuse should be assessed quantity and reliability of raw water supplies, the quality of reclaimed water, and cost effectiveness.
Choices: ['regardless of', 'with regard to', 'to the detriment of', 'on behalf of']

[Problem #554] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛??곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: One way to accelerate the flow of new ideas is to be put in difficult situations where you're likely to fail. When we fail to do something, we feel frustrated and we begin trying out other behaviors. Many ideas compete vigorously, greatly enhancing the creative process. Say you start to turn a doorknob that has always turned easily. It won't move. You turn the knob harder. Then you pull it up or push it down. Maybe you wiggle it. Eventually, you may shove or kick the door. These efforts from established behaviors will probably lead to new solutions. Creativity is an extension of .
Choices: ['how long you think', 'how you operate tools', 'what you already know', 'what your personality is']

[Problem #555] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛??곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: If you are at the seaside, and you take an old, dull, brown penny and rub it hard for a minute or two with handfuls of wet sand, the penny will come out a bright gold colour, looking as clean and new as the day it was made. Now poetry has the same effect on words as wet sand on pennies. In what seems almost a miraculous way, it brightens up words that looked dull and ordinary. Thus, poetry is perpetually .
Choices: ['cultivating your mind', 'recreating language', 'beautifying the nature', 'discovering the unknown universe']

[Problem #556] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛??쒗쁽?쇰줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Some people give up the moment an obstacle is placed in front of them. Some people doggedly continue to pursue a goal even after years of frustration and failure. What is the difference between these two people? Those who feel they are not responsible for choosing their goals and pursing them tend to believe that results are arbitrary. To them, it does not matter how hard you try or how talented you are. Being successful is all a matter of luck. Those who persevere, , recognize that they are ultimately responsible not just for pursuing their goals, but for setting them. To them, what you do matters, and giving up for no reasons does not seem very attractive.
Choices: ['however', 'moreover', 'likewise', 'therefore']

[Problem #558] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: All you have to do is this: When you feel yourself getting angry, take a long, deep breath, and as you do, say the number one to yourself. When I was growing up, my father used to count out loud to ten when he was angry with my sisters and me. ( A ) It was a strategy he used to cool down before deciding what to do next. ( B ) I've improved this strategy by incorporating the use of the breath. ( C ) Then, relax your entire body as you breathe out. ( D ) What you are doing here is clearing your mind with a mini version of a meditation exercise. The combination of counting and breathing is so relaxing that it's almost impossible to remain angry once you are finished.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #560] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Character is a respect for human beings and the right to interpret experience differently. Character admits self-interest as a natural trait, but pins its faith on man's hesitant but heartening instinct to understand and support others. Character is allergic to tyranny, irritable with ignorance and always open to improvement. Character implies the ability to laugh wholeheartedly and weep unashamedly. Character is, above all, a tremendous humility before the facts ??an automatic alliance with truth even when that truth is bitter medicine. A quality of character not mentioned by the author is .
Choices: ['freedom', 'patience', 'sympathy', 'humbleness']

[Problem #568] ??붿쓽 ?먮쫫?쇰줈 蹂댁븘 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: ?곕━留먯쓣 ?곸뼱濡??섎せ ??릿 寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #579] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Not even the bedrooms were private. The growing individualism showed itself in a desire for privacy. ( A ) In the seventeenth century middle-class and wealthier families were served by servants, who listened to their conversation as they ate. ( B ) They lived in rooms that led one to another, usually through wide double doors. ( C ) But in the eighteenth century families began to eat alone, preferring to serve themselves than to have servants listening to everything they had to say. ( D ) They also rebuilt the insides of their homes, putting in corridors, so that every person in the family had their own private bedroom.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #620] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: He knew, though, he would never become an Olympic runner, so he looked for other sports that he could play. Many people have faced great obstacles in their lives but have found ways to overcome and actually benefit from these obstacles. For example, Greg Barton, the 1984, 1988, and 1992 U.S. Olympic medalist in kayaking, was born with a serious disability. ( A ) He had deformed feet, his toes pointed inward, and as a result, he could not walk easily. Even after a series of operations, he still had limited mobility. ( B ) Even so, Greg was never defeated. First, he taught himself to walk, and even to run. Then, he competed in his high school running team. ( C ) Happily, he discovered kayaking, a perfect sport for him because it required minimal leg and foot muscles. Using his upper body strength, he was able to master the sport. ( D ) Finally, after many years of training and perseverance, Greg made the 1984 Olympic team.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #634] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: For example, some cultural groups were often portrayed as gangsters, while others were usually shown as the `good guys' who arrested them. One of the challenges we face in the world today is that a lot of the information we get about other people and places comes from the advertising and entertainment we see in the media. ( A ) You can't always trust these types of information. ( B ) To the people who make television programs and advertisements, true facts and honest opinions aren't as important as keeping you interested long enough to sell you something! ( C ) In the past, the messages we received from television programs, advertisements, and movies were full of stereotypes. ( D ) Even places were presented as stereotypes: European cities, such as Paris and Venice, were usually shown as beautiful and romantic, but cities in Africa and Asia, such as Cairo and Calcutta, were often shown as poor and overcrowded.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #649] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: We can in consequence establish relations with almost all sorts of them. Reptiles and fish may no doubt be found in swarms and shoals; they have been hatched in quantities and similar conditions have kept them together. In the case of social and gregarious mammals, the association arises not simply from a community of external forces but is sustained by an inner impulse. They are not merely like one another and so found in the same places at the same times; they like one another and so they keep together. This difference between the reptile world and the world of our human minds is one our sympathies seem unable to pass. ( A ) We cannot conceive in ourselves the swift uncomplicated urgency of a reptile's instinctive motives, its appetites, fears and hates. ( B ) We cannot understand them in their simplicity because all our motives are complicated; ours are balances and resultants and not simply urgencies. ( C ) But the mammals and birds have self-restraint and consideration for other individuals, a social appeal, a self-control that is, at its lower level, after our own fashion. ( D ) When they suffer they utter cries and make movements that rouse our feelings. We can make pets of them with a mutual recognition. They can be tamed to self-restraint towards us, domesticated and taught.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #654] ?ㅼ쓬 臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Print, however, with its standard format and type, introduced exact mass reproduction. Print transformed how knowledge itself was understood and transmitted. A manuscript is a unique and unreproducible object. ( A ) This meant that two readers separated by distance could discuss and compare identical books, right down to a specific word on a particular page. ( B ) With the introduction of consistent pagination, indexes, alphabetic ordering, and bibliographies (all unthinkable in manuscript), knowledge itself was slowly repackaged. ( C ) Textual scholarship became a cumulative science, as scholars could now gather manuscripts of, say, Aristotle's Politics and print a standard authoritative edition based on a comparison of all available copies. ( D ) This also led to the phenomenon of new and revised editions.
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #669] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: He dismally fails the first two, but redeems himself in the concluding whale episode, where he does indeed demonstrate courage, honesty, and unselfishness. Disney's work draws heavily from fairy tales, myths, and folklore, which are profuse in archetypal elements. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #699] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: This inequality is corrected by their getting in their turn better portions from kills by other people. Let us examine a situation of simple distribution such as occurs when an animal is killed in a hunt. One might expect to find the animal portioned out according to the amount of work done by each hunter to obtain it. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #708] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: Only New Zealand, New Caledonia and a few small islands peek above the waves. Lurking beneath New Zealand is a long-hidden continent called Zealandia, geologists say. But since nobody is in charge of officially designating a new continent, individual scientists will ultimately have to judge for themselves. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #715] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: [臾?15.節욌Ц 17.] As a middle-class Jew growing up in an ethnically mixed Chicago neighborhood, I was already in danger of being beaten up daily by rougher working-class boys. Becoming a bookworm would only have given them a decisive reason for beating me up. Reading and studying were more permissible for girls, but they, too, had to be careful not to get too <u>intellectual</u>, lest they acquire the stigma of being 'stuck up.'
Choices: ['athletic', 'intellectual', 'hospitable', 'inexperienced']

[Problem #736] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Some remain intensely proud of their original accent and dialect words, phrases and gestures, while others accommodate rapidly to a new environment by changing their speech habits, so that they no longer "stand out in the crowd." Our perceptions and production of speech change with time. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #757] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Some of these ailments are short-lived; others may be long-lasting. For centuries, humans have looked up at the sky and wondered what exists beyond the realm of our planet. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #777] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: It was then he remembered his experience with the glass flask, and just as quickly, he imagined that a special coating might be applied to a glass windshield to keep it from shattering. In 1903 the French chemist, Edouard Benedictus, dropped a glass flask one day on a hard floor and broke it. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #789] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: For example, the state archives of New Jersey hold more than 30,000 cubic feet of paper and 25,000 reels of microfilm. Archives are a treasure trove of material: from audio to video to newspapers, magazines and printed material?븏hich makes them indispensable to any History Detective investigation. While libraries and archives may appear the same, the differences are important. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #818] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: Thus, blood, and life-giving oxygen, are easier for the heart to circulate to the brain. People can be exposed to gravitational force, or g-force, in different ways. It can be localized, affecting only a portion of the body, as in getting slapped on the back. It can also be momentary, such as hard forces endured in a car crash. A third type of g-force is sustained, or lasting for at least several seconds. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #838] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡??뚮쭪? 寃껋??
Desc: They installed video cameras at places known for illegal crossings, and put live video feeds from the cameras on a Web site. Immigration reform is a political minefield. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #849] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 ?곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: ?쟄ow long is the tour? ?좾hat does the city tour include? ?줔o you have a list of tour packages?
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #857] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡??곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: Tribal oral history and archaeological evidence suggest that sometime between 1500 and 1700 a mudslide destroyed part of the village, covering several longhouses and sealing in their contents. From the village of Ozette on the westernmost point of Washington?셲 Olympic Peninsula, members of the Makah tribe hunted whales. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #862] 諛묒쨪 移?遺遺꾩뿉 ?ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: On January 23, the American Library <u>books of 2011. A total of 18 separate</u>
Choices: ['taken off', 'run', 'put off', 'handed']

[Problem #886] ?ㅼ쓬 湲??鍮덉뭏???ㅼ뼱媛?留먮줈 媛???곸젅??寃껋쓣 怨좊Ⅴ?쒖삤.
Desc: A 7.0 magnitude earthquake hit Haiti <u>the country in ruins.</u>
Choices: ['what left', 'leaving', 'that left', 'which leaving']

[Problem #980] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: And working offers more than financial security. Why do workaholics enjoy their jobs so much? Mostly because working offers some important advantages. It provides people with paychecks?뷲 way to earn a living. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #998] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??寃껋??
Desc: That?셲 how you forget how to do something ??forget a fact or a name, or how to do a maths calculation, or how to kick a ball at a perfect angle. Each time you repeat the same action, or thought, or recall the same memory, that particular web of connections is activated again. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #1016] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: However, bees are under threat, and the biggest offenders have been human beings. It is well known that bees are the main pollinators of the world. They help 90 percent of the world?셲 wildflowers to grow, and they also pollinate 35 percent of the world?셲 crops, including apples and tomatoes. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #1040] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: The tension is gone. Team sports offer a particularly compelling form of drama. The outcome of a game, unlike that of a scripted drama, is unknown. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]

[Problem #1052] 二쇱뼱吏?臾몄옣???ㅼ뼱媛??꾩튂濡?媛???곸젅??怨녹??
Desc: This means that caregivers will regard children, parents and other adults as important as themselves in having a voice in making decisions or giving opinions. Each person is equal in terms of human worth and dignity. (
Choices: ['洹몃뒗嫄곗쭞留먰뻽?ㅻ뒗寃껋쓣?몄젙?덈떎. ??He admitted being told a lie.', '?щ엺?ㅼ??뱀젙臾명솕, ?ш퀬泥닿퀎, 洹몃━怨좎뼵?댁뿉?섑빐臾쇰뱾?닿컙?? ??People are instilled by a specific culture, thought system, and language.', "洹몃??붿븘湲곗쓽?몄쓬?꾨찄異붿?紐삵뻽怨? ?곕씪?쒗븳怨꾩뿉?대Ⅴ??? ??She couldn't stop the baby's crying, so she was at the end of her tether.", "?섏＜媛꾨퉬媛?대━怨좎엳?대굹?붿씠?좎뵪?먯쭊?由ш??쒕떎. ??Since it has been raining for weeks, I'm getting fed up with this weather."]
